[
    {
    "learning goal": 1, 
    "question": "What is a cat?",
    "choices": ["Dog","Elephant","Turtle","Cat"],
    "answer": "Cat"
    },

    {
    "learning goal": 1, 
    "question": "What is a typical lifespan of a cat?",
    "choices": ["12-18 years","20-22 years","0-4 years","6-12 years"],
    "answer": "12-18 years"
    },
    {
    "learning goal": 1, 
    "question": "Which is NOT a breed of cat?",
    "choices": ["Siamese","British Shorthair","Persian","Poodle"],
    "answer": "Poodle"
    },
    {
    "learning goal": 1, 
    "question": "What do cats love?",
    "choices": ["Watermelon","Onions","Catnip","Dog Food"],
    "answer": "Catnip"
    },
    {
    "learning goal": 1, 
    "question": "What is a baby cat called?",
    "choices": ["Foal","Kitten","Puppy","Hatchling"],
    "answer": "Kitten"
    },


    {
    "learning goal": 2, 
    "question": "Where are the headquarters of Subaru?",
    "choices": ["Japan","Korea","China","Germany"],
    "answer": "Japan"
    },

    {
    "learning goal": 2, 
    "question": "Which car of the following is not a model of Honda?",
    "choices": ["Accord","Pilot","Camry","Civic"],
    "answer": "Camry"
    },
    {
    "learning goal": 2, 
    "question": "What is the best selling car of all time?",
    "choices": ["Toyota Corolla","Ford Model T","Volkswagen Beetle","Subaru Impreza"],
    "answer": "Toyota Corolla"
    },
    {
    "learning goal": 2, 
    "question": "What is a car?",
    "choices": ["Airplane","Boat","Car","Aircraft Carrier"],
    "answer": "Car"
    },
    {
    "learning goal": 2, 
    "question": "How many people can you safely fit into a Honda Accord?",
    "choices": ["5","4","7","13"],
    "answer": "5"
    },

    {
    "learning goal": 3, 
    "question": "What is NOT a berry?",
    "choices": ["Blueberry","Strawberry","Raspberry","Banana"],
    "answer": "Strawberry"
    },

    {
    "learning goal": 3, 
    "question": "Which of the following is considered a tropical fruit",
    "choices": ["Apple","Grape","Papaya","Orange"],
    "answer": "Papaya"
    },
    {
    "learning goal": 3, 
    "question": "What was the first vegetable grown in space?",
    "choices": ["Celery","Potato","Squash","Carrot"],
    "answer": "Potato"
    },
    {
    "learning goal": 3, 
    "question": "What apple variant is native to North America?",
    "choices": ["Crabapple","Gala","Honeycrisp","Empire"],
    "answer": "Crabapple"
    },
    {
    "learning goal": 3, 
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT a citrus fruit",
    "choices": ["Orange","Pomelo","Lime","Watermelon"],
    "answer": "Watermelon"
    },


    {
    "learning goal": 4, 
    "question": "Which is not a starter pokemon in Pokemon Emerald?",
    "choices": ["Mudkip","Treeko","Torchic","Squirtle"],
    "answer": "Squirtle"
    },

    {
    "learning goal": 4, 
    "question": "what is the bestselling Pokemon game?",
    "choices": ["Pokemon Red/Green/Blue","Pokemon Leafgreen/Firered","Pokemon Heartgold/Soulsilver","Pokemon Pearl/Diamond"],
    "answer": "Pokemon Red/Green/Blue"
    },
    {
    "learning goal": 4, 
    "question": "Which pokemon is the only pokemon that can devolve?",
    "choices": ["Raichu","Slowbro","Machamp","Torterra"],
    "answer": "Slowbro"
    },
    {
    "learning goal": 4, 
    "question": "What was the first pokemon ever created?",
    "choices": ["Pikachu","Rayquaza","Rhydon","Pidgey"],
    "answer": "Rhydon"
    },
    {
    "learning goal": 4, 
    "question": "what type of Pokemon are effective against Normal type Pokemon?",
    "choices": ["Fighting","Dragon","Ice","Bug"],
    "answer": "Fighting"
    }


    




]